Lynn Hershman-Leeson Papers M1452
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Film Projects: Correspondence and Materials, 2
  - Subseries 2.12: The Floating Museum 1974-1978, 2.12
    - Darryl Sapien 1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Peter Wiehl 1974 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Floating Museum 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Writings/Philosophy 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Finances 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Funding/Grants 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Media [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Media [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Media [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Media [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases 1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Publicity 1974 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Floating Museum Brochure [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Floating Museum Brochure [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Stationary 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Membership Application 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Writings 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Photography 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Free Space 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Restructuring the Public Opinion of Jerry Rubin 1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Global Space Invasion 1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Motion [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Motion [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - (H)errata 1974 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Angel Island 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Leila & the Snakes 1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Global Passport 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Crime in the Streets 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Telemetry [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Telemetry [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Exposures 1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bologna International Art Fair 1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Garam Gudang Group 1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Artomat 1974 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Space/Time/Sound-1970s 1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Revolving Sites 1974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - San Quentin Mural Project - Invitations 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - San Quentin Mural Project - Correspondence 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - San Quentin Mural Project - Photography 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - San Quentin Mural Project - Press 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - San Quentin Mural Project - Writings 1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Michael Asher 1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Eleanor Antin 1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Beeldend Theater [1 of 2] 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Beeldend Theater [2 of 2] 1974 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Paul Cotton 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Peter D'Agostino 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Jill Scott 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Reese Williams 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Rose Marie Prins 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Irini Nadel 1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Gordon Morris 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Michelle Larson 1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 2.13: Lady Luck, 2.13
    - Lady Luck 1975 1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Brochures 1975 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1975 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Exhibitions 1975 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Conceptual Research and Development 1975 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Photographs 1975 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Film - "Energy Perspectives"]\ 1975 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Film - "Lady Luck" 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Film - "Lady Luck" 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.14: Lorna, 2.14
    - Lorna 1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Conceptual Research 1979 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Production Notes 1979 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Storyboard 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Script 1979 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Technical Information 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Disk Branching System 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Photography (negatives, contact sheets, 7x5s) 1979 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - DVD: "the world's first video game, Lorna" 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Engagement 1979 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Personal 1979 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Production 1979 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Exhibition and Screening Brochures 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Catalogue 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Airline Ticket Giveaway 1979 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Media (1 of 2) 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Media (2 of 2) 1979 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2.15: Myth America (MAMCO), 2.15
    - Myth America - Mayfield Mall - Project Development 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Mayfield Mall - Public Relations material (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Myth America Corp 1979-1980 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - MAMCO Timeline 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - MAMCO Artifacts 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Invoices 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Art Purchase Program 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Budget/Finances 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Reciepts 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Project Proposal - Mayfield 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Mayfield 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Mayfield Mall Blueprints 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Mayfield 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Herve Fiscer 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Dan Graham 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Bill Lundberg 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Kathryn Keller 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Michelangelo Pistoletto 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Richard Prince 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Mierle Ukeles 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2.16: New York Hotels, 2.16
    - New York Hotels (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Catalogues [1 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Catalogues [2 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Catalogues [3 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Catalogues [4 of 4] (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Press (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hotel Postcards [1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hotel Postcards [2 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Photographs [1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Photographs [2 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2.17: Non-Credited Americans, 2.17
    - Non-Credited Americans 1981 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Design Development 1981 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1981 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition 1981 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Photography 1981 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Expenses 1981 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Media 1981 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2.18: Paranoid Mirror, 2.18
    - Paranoid Mirror 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Project Proposal 1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Materials List 1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Software Schematics 1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Technical Notes 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Operating Instructions 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Contact Information 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Photographs 1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Receipts 1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Seattle Art Museum Contract 1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - SAM Budget 1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - SAM Correspondence 1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - SAM PR Release 1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - SAM Catalogue Correspondece 1995 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - SAM Catalogue Essays 1995 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - SAM Panel 1995 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Seattle Media 1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Digital Meditations 1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Pilkington-Osloff Fine Arts, Inc. 1995 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous 1995 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2.19: Reforming Familiar Environments, 2.19
    - Reforming Familiar Environments 1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Instruction Manuals [1 of 2] 1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Instruction Manuals [2 of 2] 1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Photographs 1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous 1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Media 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2.20: A Room of One's Own, 2.20
    - "A Room of One's Own" 1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Installation Instructions 1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Video Installation Instructions 1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous 1990 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 2.21: Running Fences, 2.21
    - Correspondence 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence re: Hershman credit as Artisitic Director for Running Fences (Photocopies) 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Research and Development; includes Annual Report 1974, California Coastal Zone Commmission; Water Resources Development: California, 1975, U.S. Army Corps of Engineers; "Christo's Running Fence," statement of purpose and timeline prepared by Ernest C. Harris, senior staff engineer, Ken R. White Company; computation sheets for the stability and strength of the Running Fence, prepared by the Ken R. White Company; "Idea #2. Running Fence. Lynn Hershman 1982," collage composed of sketch with postcard annotations; "Running Fence co-sponsorship agreement regarding the purchase of Running Fence by the Running Fence Corporation; message to Ted Dougherty, Christo, Mary Abell and Peter Selz from Ernie H. regarding an engineering detail of the Running Fence. 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Maps; includes Road map of Petaluma and Sonoma County with annotated route of the Running Fence and miscellaneous notes; blueprint map, detailing areas between Two Rock and Glen Ellen; blueprint map, detailing areas between Bodega Bay and Two Rock; blueprint map, detailing areas between Bodega Bay (Head)/Jenner and Two Rock; blueprint map, detailing areas between Valley Ford and Cotati; blueprint detailing property holdings along path of the Running Fence, with list of owners; large blueprint map detailing areas between Bodega Bay and Denman Flat, showijng route of the fence, adjacent roads and gates, location of truck, motor bikes, and foot monitors. ` 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Contracts and Agreements; includes "Running Fence General Information:" report describing project and timeline of the legal history of the project; Use Permit application Sonoma County Planning Department with photocopied attachment title pages (no attached documents); Final Agenda North Central Coast Regional Commission, Thursday April 17, 1975 (Consent Calendar item d. Running Fence); Report of Test No. 2 Run B on a Prototype Section of Christo's Running Fence (Ken R. White Co. and A and H Builders); contract between Running Fence Corporation and Lynn Hershman as Associate Director, three contract definitions were changed and dated April 25, 1975, New York; Maysles Films, Inc. release form with signatures; California Coastal Zone Conservation Commission Agenda, 6/17/75 (Running Fence, item 8f); Easement Agreement between Edward H. and Jerrold E. Peterson and the Running Fence Corp., n.d.; Board of Supervisors County of Marin Agenda, 2/4/75 (Running Fence item #47); Agreement between Lynn Hershman and the Running Fence Corporation, detailing Hershman's terms and duties, dated 1/1/1974; "Application for Employment - Installation and Display Workers, Christo's Running Fence - Sonoma-Marin Counties," blank contract forms; "Executed Easement Agreements for Running Fence (From West to East)," lists parcel numbers, names and addresses. 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Photos 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Postcards 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Media [1 of 2] (Photocopies) 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Media [2 of 2] 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Stationery 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2.22: Technolust, 2.22
    - Technolust Budget 2002 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Day Out of Days 2002 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Custer Stages & Locations 2002 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Lighting & Grip 2002 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Camera 2002 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Check Request(s) 2002 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Travel 2002 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Insurance 2002 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Union(s) 2002 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Calls Sheets/Prod. Reports 2002 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Budget(s) 2002 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - American Property Exchange 2002 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Cast List 2002 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Catering 2002 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Headshots 2002 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Hotel - Compton Place 2002 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Hotel - Majestic 2002 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Hotel/Travel Producers 2002 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Interns 2002 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Post Production 2002 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Publicity 2002 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Master Script 2002 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Script 2002 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Teknolust Summary 2002 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Article on Hershman 2002 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Resumes 2002 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Security 2002 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - SAG 2002 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Stage Misc. 2002 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Taft Hartley 2002 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Transportation 2002 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Workers Camp 2002 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Yamamoto 2002 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - E-mail/Correspondence 2002 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Insurance 2002 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Petty Cash Envelopes 2002 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Petty Cash Envelopes 2002 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Tekno 2002 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Teknolust 1-3 (3.5 floppy) 2002 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Tekno Art #1-3 (zip disk) 2002 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 2.23: Virtual Love, 2.23
    - Psychedelics, Cyberpunks: Early 90s liberalism in the Bay Area 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - "Danish Film Institute Workshop" advertisement scrap (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Cast List, Polaroid (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Phone numbers (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Music: Miscellaneous 1992 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "Zweite Deutsche Fernsehen": ZDF Nov 1990 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - VR Contacts (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations Oct 1991 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Camera Ops (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Resources (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Film Company Correspondences 1992 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Script: Actor's File (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Virtual Reality (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - "Interaktiivisen mediataiteen nayttely": Documents pertaining to VL (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Virtual Reality (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Virtual Love Story Development Materials (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Misc: Various Drafts, etc.. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Two Copies: Third Script Draft "Virtual Love" (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Detailed Rehearsal Preparations, Notes (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Actress Photos (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Graphic Art (publicity) (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Press Materials pertaining to slain actress (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - "Terminal Reading: On Being Sound-Bitten" by Todd Gitlin (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - "American Montage" First Script Draft Sept 1991 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Various Research: newspapers, articles, etc.. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Various; "The Picture After the Last Picture" by Peter Weibel (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Arts Brochure (German) (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Technical Brochure, article (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Correspondences (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Brochures: "...World's First Interactive Video Art Disc Game" (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Virtual Love: Sets and Actor info (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Virtual Love Scripts (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Virtual Love Scripts (2 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.24: 25 Windows, 2.24
    - 25 Windows 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Conceptual Research and Development 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Itinerary 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Design Development 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Window Survey 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Window Design 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Expenses 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Project Announcements 1975 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Project Film and Music 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Media; includes New York, Ms., photocopies, articles 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Negatives 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Contact Prints 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Photographs 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Photographs 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Photographs (1 of 2) 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Photographs (2 of 2) 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 2 View-Masters and 3 picture reels 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Roll of papers: "2 Panels Bill Blass" 1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Early Writings, 3
  - Leaping the Fence [1 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Leaping the Fence [2 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Cummings, Pauline (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Lynn Hershman - Artlife (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Museum Newpapers (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Energy Perspectives (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Prisoners of Paradise Publicity/Press (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Prisoners of Paradise Documentation (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Prisoners of Paradise Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Prisoners of Paradise Invoices (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Art in the Embassies Program (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - CCAC Alumni Exhibition (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Third Bucknell Annual Drawing Exhibition/1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Art and Urban Resources [empty] (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Artists - Soap Box Derby (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Academy of Art College (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Artwatch (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Lynn - Making It As An Artist (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Writings by Lynn - Early Book Art Life (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Writings by Lynn - Art Life Early Book (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Writings by Lynn - Artlife (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Chimera Monograph - Letters/Notes (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Chimera Monograph - Rough Draft (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Chimera Monograph - Rough Draft [1 of 3] (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Chimera Monograph - Rough Draft [2 of 3] (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chimera Monograph - Rough Draft [3 of 3] (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Administrative Files, 4
  - Forthcoming Photography/Essay Publication 2002 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "Digital Venus II" 1996 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - "Constructing Roberta Breitmore", 1975 2002 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - "Epicenter: SF Bay Area Artists..." 2002 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Safe Haven-Same/Difference August 6-September 7, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - "Imposters" Anthony Downey April 2002 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - "Digital Transformations: The Media..." Lori Landay June 2, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - "Born in Cyberspace" Dennis Conroy October 2002 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - "Dynamic Duo: Tilda & Lynn..." Jason McBride September 9, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - "Cyborgs are People, Too" Dashka Slater October 2002 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - "A Study of Mothers & Daughters" Loren King April 27, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - "Sundance Fest: Teknolust" David Rooney March 18-24, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - "Teknolust" Eric June 25, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - "Mum's the Word" Peter Keough April 27, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - "Rocky Mountain High" Sean Smith April 2002 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - "Teknolust" Anonymous June 9, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - "Teknolust" Seattle Post Intelligencer June 7, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - "Teknolust" Jennifer Albert June 25, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - "Teknolust" SGN June 7, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - "Teknolust" May 28, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - "Teknolust" Harold Hellman May 27, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - "Seattle International Film" Seattle Post Intelligencer May 24, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - "Frankenstein, With All-Female Parts" Tank Menzies March 2002 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - "IFP/West Congratulates Our Members..." IFP WEST Calendar January 2002 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - "Audrey Flack's Still Lifes" Katherine Hauser Fall 2001/Winter 2002 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Teknolust Press Kit (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - "Skouras Follows 'Teknolust Trail" Chris Gardner May 20, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - "The Wonders of Genetics Breed..." Steven Henry Madoff May 26, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - "HD Basics: Renting & Shooting" Robert Harrison December 2002 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - "Film Institute List Sealed..." Ruthe Stein June 7, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - "Salute to Big Alma" Merla Zellerbach July 2002 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - "Norwegian Comedy 'Elling' Named..." Seattle Post Intelligencer June 7, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - "Seattle International Film Festival" June 25, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - "Psycho Comic, Stylish Cyberdrama..." Moira MacDonald June 11, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - "Three Directors Bring Films..." Moira MacDonald May 24, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - "Get Reel!" Katrine Larsen May 2002 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Epicenter (The Book) (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Capturing Light: Masterpieces of CA Photography June 2001 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Avatars & Others September 15, 2001-November 4, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Double Life May 11-August 12, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Lynn Hershman Media and Identity January 10, 2001-February 25, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Beyond Boundaries January 27, 2001-March 25, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Telematic Connections: The Virtual Embrace February 7, 2001-March 25, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - The Media Tors: The Social Life of Digital Art September 23, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Visual Worlds: An Exhibition exploring visuality in the age of globalization September 28 - October 31, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Madchen Reden March 21, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Festival Films De Femmes International March 23-April 2, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Viper 21 Intl. Festival for Film, Video, & New Media October 24-28, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - 14th Virginia Film Festival October 25-28, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Akt 1/ Akt 2/ Akt 3 November 9-December 1, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Recontres Internationales de Cinema October 31-November 11, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - ICI Independent Curators International 2001 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Women, the City, and Technology March 10, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Eye and Thou Conference March 24-25, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Avatare Und Andere September 14-November 4, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Networks to Nanosystems November 8, 2001-November 14, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - "De osynliga systrarna" Bang 2001 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - "Private I, Private Eye, 2001" CTRL [SPACE] 2001 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Women Artists in the 20th and 21st Century 2001 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "Local Filmmakers Anxiously Waiting" Ruthe Stein November 16, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - "Saving it All for Oscar" Edward Guthmann November 13, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Dialogues: Bodies, Presences... 2001 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - The F-Word Project 2001 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Double Life (The Book) 2001 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Performance Artists Talking in the Eighties 2000 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Maria Roth Interview 2000 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - In Search of the Virtual and the Real 2000 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Berin Golonu's Surveillance Presentation 2000 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Linking up with Ada 2000 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Conceiving Ada DVD Reviews 2000 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Facets Video Catalog Supplement November 18, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Identity is Provisional 2000 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - "Lynn Hershman" 2000 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Sundance Hopefuls Get News Monday 2000 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Willie Brown Swears in Commissioners 2000 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - AC Ad for Ada DVD Sweepstakes Prize 2000 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Art Sale 2000 December 1, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - MFA Thesis Exhibition 2000 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Art Studio 117: Exp. Documentary Class Article February 2000 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Jim Davis March 24, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Lab 5 June 2-30, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - The Self is Something Else June 7, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Media City - Seoul 2000 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - CD ROM (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - University of California 1993 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - University of California 1993 (Box 103, Folder 3)